And what else do we have?
Nothing for now.
So I click on generate and it asks us to sign in, you know?
So this is required.
This seems to be required when it comes to using firefly.
We need to sign in or sign up.
So I do that with continuing my by continuing with my Google account.
So I don't already have any firefly or Adobe accounts.
I just do have a Google account and I want to continue with that.
I click on continue with Google and I wait.
Until the least of my Google accounts are appear and I will be asked to choose among them.
So as you see, we can choose an account to continue to Adobe.
I choose this one and I just click and wait.
And as you see, it's signing to Adobe.
Google will allow Adobe to access these info.
I click continue.
I see new problems.
And after all, as you see, we have found an existing Adobe account.
I used to have one.
I just said I don't have any but I used to have one.
So I can connect it with Google or, yep, I click connect with Google.
So as you see, that's all, the firefly will be reloaded for me, the entire web page.
And then I will probably be signed in.